{"title": ["Present Simple: Positive, Negative, Question", "Verbs - Jobs", "Personal pronouns and possessive adjectives"], "count": 60, "Question0": {"question": "She _____ a uniform.", "example": ["A) wear ", "B) to wear ", "C) wearing ", "D) wears"], "answer": "D"}, "Question1": {"question": "He _____ his car every weekend.", "example": ["A) wash ", "B) washes ", "C) washing ", "D) washed"], "answer": "B"}, "Question2": {"question": "Rosemary _____ three languages.", "example": ["A) speaks ", "B) talks ", "C) tells ", "D) know"], "answer": "A"}, "Question3": {"question": "My dad _____ at 7 o\u2019clock everyday.", "example": ["A) stands up ", "B) looks up ", "C) gets up ", "D) jumps up"], "answer": "C"}, "Question4": {"question": "Isabel is a flight attendant. She _____ passengers.", "example": ["A) serve ", "B) to serve ", "C) serves ", "D) serving"], "answer": "C"}, "Question5": {"question": "Their son _____ in this hospital.", "example": ["A) works ", "B) begins ", "C) starts ", "D) likes"], "answer": "A"}, "Question6": {"question": "Jim\u2019s a postman. He _____ letters to people.", "example": ["A) answers ", "B) works ", "C) delivers ", "D) serves"], "answer": "C"}, "Question7": {"question": "Jane\u2019s a doctor. She _____ ill people.", "example": ["A) looks at ", "B) speaks to ", "C) helps ", "D) serves drinks"], "answer": "C"}, "Question8": {"question": "Bern _____ in a flat in Birmingham.", "example": ["A) lives ", "B) stands ", "C) has ", "D) wants"], "answer": "A"}, "Question9": {"question": "Nancy\u2019s uncle is a pilot. He _____ all over the world.", "example": ["A) goes ", "B) sees ", "C) travels ", "D) delivers"], "answer": "C"}, "Question10": {"question": "In winter Sheila _____ skiing and in summer _____ tennis.", "example": ["A) makes / plays ", "B) goes / plays", "C) does / plays ", "D) starts / *"], "answer": "B"}, "Question11": {"question": "My friend\u2019s son _____ Turkish and English at university.", "example": ["A) has ", "B) plays ", "C) studies ", "D) goes"], "answer": "C"}, "Question12": {"question": "Most of the people _____ work at 8 o\u2019clock every morning.", "example": ["A) finishes ", "B) goes ", "C) does ", "D) starts"], "answer": "D"}, "Question13": {"question": "A: _____ does Tony Blair live? / B: In Great Britain.", "example": ["A) When ", "B) Where ", "C) What time ", "D) How"], "answer": "B"}, "Question14": {"question": "_____ does your father do in his free time?", "example": ["A) Why ", "B) What kind ", "C) How many ", "D) What"], "answer": "D"}, "Question15": {"question": "_____ does Andy\u2019s little brother play with?", "example": ["A) Who ", "B) Why ", "C) How old ", "D) Where"], "answer": "A"}, "Question16": {"question": "A: _____ does Natalie\u2019s nephew do? / B: He\u2019s an architect.", "example": ["A) How ", "B) Whom ", "C) When ", "D) What"], "answer": "D"}, "Question17": {"question": "A: _____ does it rain here? / B: Mostly in summer and winter.", "example": ["A) When / Why ", "B) Why / How", "C) What time / Whom ", "D) When / What about"], "answer": "D"}, "Question18": {"question": "A: _____ does Anthony go to work? / B: _____ bus.", "example": ["A) How / By ", "B) How well / On", "C) What kind / In ", "D) How / In"], "answer": "A"}, "Question19": {"question": "She _____ from England.", "example": ["A) come ", "B) comes ", "C) don\u2019t come ", "D) goes"], "answer": "B"}, "Question20": {"question": "_____ she _____ French?", "example": ["A) Do / speaks ", "B) Does / speaks", "C) Does / speak ", "D) Is / speak"], "answer": "C"}, "Question21": {"question": "She _____ _____ from America.", "example": ["A) don\u2019t comes ", "B) doesn\u2019t come", "C) doesn\u2019t comes ", "D) does comes"], "answer": "B"}, "Question22": {"question": "Every time he _____ a glass of lemonade before breakfast.", "example": ["A) is ", "B) have ", "C) has ", "D) does"], "answer": "C"}, "Question23": {"question": "_____ he _____ three children?", "example": ["A) Does / have ", "B) Does / has ", "C) Do / have ", "D) Has / have"], "answer": "A"}, "Question24": {"question": "_____ a shower.", "example": ["A) Come ", "B) Go ", "C) Have ", "D) Has"], "answer": "C"}, "Question25": {"question": "_____ the phone.", "example": ["A) Go ", "B) Read ", "C) Look ", "D) Answer"], "answer": "D"}, "Question26": {"question": "She _____ a white coat.", "example": ["A) wear ", "B) wears ", "C) does wear ", "D) have"], "answer": "B"}, "Question27": {"question": "_____ a magazine.", "example": ["A) Go ", "B) Read ", "C) Live ", "D) Has"], "answer": "B"}, "Question28": {"question": "Our teacher gives _____ a lot of homework.", "example": ["A) our ", "B) us ", "C) her ", "D) his"], "answer": "B"}, "Question29": {"question": "He _____ television every evening.", "example": ["A) watch ", "B) watches ", "C) see ", "D) buy"], "answer": "B"}, "Question30": {"question": "At ten we go _____ bed.", "example": ["A) in ", "B) on ", "C) to ", "D) sleep"], "answer": "C"}, "Question31": {"question": "He picks up the apples _____ the tree.", "example": ["A) for ", "B) from ", "C) on ", "D) at"], "answer": "B"}, "Question32": {"question": "Get _____ the bus.", "example": ["A) on ", "B) in ", "C) to ", "D) out"], "answer": "A"}, "Question33": {"question": "She lives _____ Switzerland.", "example": ["A) at ", "B) on ", "C) in ", "D) city"], "answer": "C"}, "Question34": {"question": "A nurse looks _____ people in hospital.", "example": ["A) at ", "B) for ", "C) after ", "D) helps"], "answer": "C"}, "Question35": {"question": "There\u2019s a letter _____ you.", "example": ["A) for ", "B) to ", "C) about ", "D) on"], "answer": "A"}, "Question36": {"question": "Tourists come _____ boat.", "example": ["A) by ", "B) to ", "C) of ", "D) with"], "answer": "A"}, "Question37": {"question": "He drives the children _____ school.", "example": ["A) of ", "B) at ", "C) to ", "D) go"], "answer": "C"}, "Question38": {"question": "He speaks to people _____ his radio.", "example": ["A) at ", "B) on ", "C) of ", "D) in"], "answer": "B"}, "Question39": {"question": "She likes going _____ walks _____ summer.", "example": ["A) for / at ", "B) to / at ", "C) for / in ", "D) on / at"], "answer": "C"}, "Question40": {"question": "She goes skiing _____ her free time.", "example": ["A) in ", "B) on ", "C) at ", "D) of"], "answer": "A"}, "Question41": {"question": "He works _____ an undertaker.", "example": ["A) as ", "B) for ", "C) of ", "D) in"], "answer": "A"}, "Question42": {"question": "\u201cDoes she live in Australia?\u201d / \u201cNo, she _____.\u201d", "example": ["A) do ", "B) does ", "C) don\u2019t ", "D) doesn\u2019t"], "answer": "D"}, "Question43": {"question": "We _____ _____ watching television.", "example": ["A) doesn\u2019t like ", "B) do like ", "C) doesn\u2019t like ", "D) don\u2019t like"], "answer": "D"}, "Question44": {"question": "He _____ to help people.", "example": ["A) flies ", "B) likes ", "C) runs ", "D) swim"], "answer": "B"}, "Question45": {"question": "_____ _____ languages does she speak?", "example": ["A) How much ", "B) How many ", "C) Why ", "D) Where"], "answer": "B"}, "Question46": {"question": "_____ sells things.", "example": ["A) A postman ", "B) A nurse ", "C) A doctor ", "D) A shopkeeper"], "answer": "D"}, "Question47": {"question": "A barman _____.", "example": ["A) sells things ", "B) serves drinks", "C) delivers letters ", "D) drinks a lot"], "answer": "B"}, "Question48": {"question": "_____ _____ looks after money.", "example": ["A) A nurse ", "B) A postman", "C) An accountant ", "D) A dentist"], "answer": "C"}, "Question49": {"question": "__________ designs buildings.", "example": ["A) A pilot ", "B) An architect", "C) An interpreter ", "D) An engineer"], "answer": "B"}, "Question50": {"question": "He lives ____ an island _____ the west of Scotland.", "example": ["A) on / in ", "B) in / in ", "C) on / on ", "D) in / at"], "answer": "A"}, "Question51": {"question": "She\u2019s married _____ an American man.", "example": ["A) with ", "B) for ", "C) to ", "D) on"], "answer": "C"}, "Question52": {"question": "He _____ listening _____ music.", "example": ["A) like / to ", "B) likes / to ", "C) likes / of ", "D) likes / with"], "answer": "B"}, "Question53": {"question": "\u201cHow _____ he _____ to work?\u201d / \u201cBy car.\u201d", "example": ["A) do / go ", "B) does / goes ", "C) does / go ", "D) does / play"], "answer": "C"}, "Question54": {"question": "Anna likes Joanna, but Maria doesn\u2019t like _____.", "example": ["A) her ", "B) them ", "C) your ", "D) their"], "answer": "A"}, "Question55": {"question": "That\u2019s my dictionary. Can I have ___ back please?", "example": ["A) it ", "B) you ", "C) them ", "D) my"], "answer": "A"}, "Question56": {"question": "Philippe _____ in London.", "example": ["A) work ", "B) starts ", "C) comes ", "D) lives"], "answer": "D"}, "Question57": {"question": "\u201c_____ he married?\u201d / \u201cNo, he _____.\u201d", "example": ["A) Is / doesn\u2019t ", "B) Does / isn\u2019t ", "C) Is / isn\u2019t ", "D) Does / is"], "answer": "C"}, "Question58": {"question": "\u201cWhat _____ she do?\u201d / \u201cShe is an interpreter.\u201d", "example": ["A) is ", "B) do ", "C) does ", "D) are"], "answer": "C"}, "Question59": {"question": "_____ he sleep well?", "example": ["A) Has ", "B) Have ", "C) Do ", "D) Does"], "answer": "D"}}